<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Area>
  <AreaData>
    <Name>Forest Road</Name>
    <Info></Info>
    <VnumStart>50900</VnumStart>
    <VnumEnd>50999</VnumEnd>
    <Builders></Builders>
    <Security>0</Security>
    <Credits></Credits>
  </AreaData>
  <Rooms>
    <Room>
      <VNum>50900</VNum>
      <Name>Middle of a bridge crossing the dark river</Name>
      <Description>As you step into the middle of the bridge crossing the dark river, you can
feel a slight sway beneath your feet. The sound of rushing water echoes all
around you, as the river flows rapidly beneath the sturdy wooden planks.
Looking down over the edge, you see the frothy white water churning below.
The sides of the bridge rise up high, with thick wooden beams supporting
the structure on either side. You can see straight ahead to the other side
of the river, where the path continues on, winding its way through the
trees beyond. Looking back the way you came, you can see the winding path
leading to the bridge, and the dark, dense forest beyond. The air is cool
and crisp, with a faint scent of damp wood and earth. The only sounds are
the rushing water and the occasional creaking of the bridge as it sways
gently in the wind. Despite the solitude, there is a sense of safety and
security on the sturdy bridge, allowing you to take in the breathtaking
scenery around you.</Description>
      <Sector>Road</Sector>
      <Flags></Flags>
      <Exits>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>North</Direction>
          <Destination>51521</Destination>
          <Display>the door north</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>South</Direction>
          <Destination>50901</Destination>
          <Display>the door south</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
      </Exits>
      <ExtraDescriptions />
    </Room>
    <Room>
      <VNum>50901</VNum>
      <Name>End of the bridge crossing the dark river</Name>
      <Description>As you step onto the end of the bridge crossing the dark river, you feel
the wooden planks become more solid beneath your feet. The rushing sound of
the water below fades as you leave the middle of the river and enter the
quiet bank. The path ahead of you widens into a well-trodden trail, lined
with trees on either side. The forest beyond the trees is dense and dark,
with the occasional shaft of sunlight breaking through the canopy. Looking
back at the bridge, you can see its impressive structure stretching out
behind you, with the river flowing steadily beneath it. The air is fresh
and cool, with the faint scent of damp earth and foliage. You can hear the
chirping of birds and the rustling of leaves in the breeze. There is a
sense of completion at the end of the bridge, a feeling of having crossed a
threshold into a new space. You are now in the midst of a new journey, with
new adventures waiting to be discovered beyond the winding path ahead.</Description>
      <Sector>Road</Sector>
      <Flags></Flags>
      <Exits>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>North</Direction>
          <Destination>50900</Destination>
          <Display>the door north</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>South</Direction>
          <Destination>50902</Destination>
          <Display>the door south</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
      </Exits>
      <ExtraDescriptions />
    </Room>
    <Room>
      <VNum>50902</VNum>
      <Name>The Forest Road</Name>
      <Description>The path winds its way through a dense forest, with tall trees rising up on
either side, their branches intermingling overhead to form a natural
archway. The air is cool and damp, with the scent of earth and foliage
filling your senses. Sunlight filters down through the leaves, casting
dappled shadows on the path before you. The ground beneath your feet is
soft and springy, covered in a layer of fallen leaves and moss. As you
walk, you can hear the crunching of twigs and leaves beneath your feet,
along with the rustling of animals in the underbrush. The occasional bird
call breaks the peaceful silence, adding to the natural symphony around
you.</Description>
      <Sector>Road</Sector>
      <Flags></Flags>
      <Exits>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>North</Direction>
          <Destination>50901</Destination>
          <Display>the door north</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>South</Direction>
          <Destination>50903</Destination>
          <Display>the door south</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
      </Exits>
      <ExtraDescriptions />
    </Room>
    <Room>
      <VNum>50903</VNum>
      <Name>The Forest Road</Name>
      <Description>The path winds its way through a dense forest, with towering trees on
either side casting long shadows over the path. The air is cool and
refreshing, carrying the scents of earth, leaves, and wildflowers. Sunlight
filters down through the trees, dappling the path with patches of golden
light. As you look ahead, you can see that the forest road continues to the
north and west, winding its way deeper into the heart of the forest. The
path is well-maintained and easy to follow, with occasional markers guiding
the way. As you walk, you can hear the chirping of birds and the rustling
of leaves in the gentle breeze. The forest around you is alive with
activity, with squirrels and rabbits darting across the path and the
occasional deer grazing in a clearing. Despite the feeling of solitude,
there is a sense of safety and security in this natural setting, with the
forest road providing a clear and easy path through the wilderness. The
sense of adventure and possibility is palpable, as the forest road
continues to beckon you further into the unknown.</Description>
      <Sector>Road</Sector>
      <Flags></Flags>
      <Exits>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>North</Direction>
          <Destination>50902</Destination>
          <Display>the door north</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>West</Direction>
          <Destination>50904</Destination>
          <Display>the door west</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
      </Exits>
      <ExtraDescriptions />
    </Room>
    <Room>
      <VNum>50904</VNum>
      <Name>The Forest Road</Name>
      <Description>The path winds its way through a dense forest, with tall trees on either
side creating a natural canopy overhead. The air is cool and fresh,
carrying the scents of pine and earth. Sunlight filters through the leaves,
casting dappled shadows on the path before you. Looking ahead, you can see
that the forest road continues to the east and south, leading deeper into
the heart of the wilderness. The path is well-maintained, with occasional
markers guiding the way. As you walk, you can hear the rustling of leaves
in the gentle breeze, along with the occasional bird call or rustling of
small animals in the underbrush. The forest around you is alive with
activity, with the occasional squirrel or rabbit darting across the path.
Despite the feeling of solitude, there is a sense of safety and security on
the forest road, with the well-defined path providing a clear route through
the wilderness. The forest road invites you to explore further into the
natural world, offering a sense of adventure and possibility with each step
you take.</Description>
      <Sector>Road</Sector>
      <Flags></Flags>
      <Exits>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>East</Direction>
          <Destination>50903</Destination>
          <Display>the door east</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>South</Direction>
          <Destination>50905</Destination>
          <Display>the door south</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
      </Exits>
      <ExtraDescriptions />
    </Room>
    <Room>
      <VNum>50905</VNum>
      <Name>The Forest Road</Name>
      <Description>The path winds its way through a dense forest, with towering trees on
either side creating a natural archway overhead. The air is cool and fresh,
carrying the scents of pine and earth. Sunlight filters through the leaves,
casting dappled shadows on the path before you. Looking ahead, you can see
that the forest road continues to the north and south, leading deeper into
the heart of the wilderness. The path is well-maintained, with occasional
markers guiding the way. As you walk, you can hear the rustling of leaves
in the gentle breeze, along with the occasional bird call or rustling of
small animals in the underbrush. The forest around you is alive with
activity, with the occasional squirrel or rabbit darting across the path.</Description>
      <Sector>Road</Sector>
      <Flags></Flags>
      <Exits>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>North</Direction>
          <Destination>50904</Destination>
          <Display>the door north</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>South</Direction>
          <Destination>50906</Destination>
          <Display>the door south</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
      </Exits>
      <ExtraDescriptions />
    </Room>
    <Room>
      <VNum>50906</VNum>
      <Name>The Forest Road</Name>
      <Description>The path winds its way through a dense forest, with towering trees on
either side creating a natural archway overhead. The air is cool and fresh,
carrying the scents of pine and earth. Sunlight filters through the leaves,
casting dappled shadows on the path before you. Looking ahead, you can see
that the forest road continues to the north and south, leading deeper into
the heart of the wilderness. The path is well-maintained, with occasional
markers guiding the way. As you walk, you can hear the rustling of leaves
in the gentle breeze, along with the occasional bird call or rustling of
small animals in the underbrush. The forest around you is alive with
activity, with the occasional squirrel or rabbit darting across the path.</Description>
      <Sector>Road</Sector>
      <Flags></Flags>
      <Exits>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>North</Direction>
          <Destination>50905</Destination>
          <Display>the door north</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>South</Direction>
          <Destination>50907</Destination>
          <Display>the door south</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
      </Exits>
      <ExtraDescriptions />
    </Room>
    <Room>
      <VNum>50907</VNum>
      <Name>The Forest Road</Name>
      <Description>The road stretches out before you, winding through the dense forest to the
north and west. The ground beneath your feet is soft and springy, covered
in a layer of fallen leaves and pine needles. The air is cool and
refreshing, carrying the scents of earth and foliage. The forest around you
is alive with activity, with the occasional rustle of leaves and the
distant call of a bird. The forest road itself is well-worn, with deep ruts
in the earth and occasional signs of travelers passing through. Despite the
feeling of isolation in the wilderness, there is a sense of community and
connection on the forest road. The road itself is a symbol of the shared
journey through the wild, with travelers from all walks of life passing
through. As you walk along the forest road, you feel a sense of excitement
and anticipation for the adventures that lie ahead. The road to the north
and west offers the promise of further exploration and discovery, leading
deeper into the untamed wilderness.</Description>
      <Sector>Road</Sector>
      <Flags></Flags>
      <Exits>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>North</Direction>
          <Destination>50906</Destination>
          <Display>the door north</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>West</Direction>
          <Destination>50908</Destination>
          <Display>the door west</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
      </Exits>
      <ExtraDescriptions />
    </Room>
    <Room>
      <VNum>50908</VNum>
      <Name>The Forest Road</Name>
      <Description>The road stretches out before you, winding through the dense forest to the
west and east. The ground beneath your feet is soft and springy, covered in
a layer of fallen leaves and pine needles. The air is cool and refreshing,
carrying the scents of earth and foliage. The forest around you is alive
with activity, with the occasional rustle of leaves and the distant call of
a bird. The forest road itself is well-worn, with deep ruts in the earth
and occasional signs of travelers passing through. Despite the feeling of
isolation in the wilderness, there is a sense of community and connection
on the forest road. The road itself is a symbol of the shared journey
through the wild, with travelers from all walks of life passing through. As
you walk along the forest road, you feel a sense of excitement and
anticipation for the adventures that lie ahead. The road to the west and
east offers the promise of further exploration and discovery, leading
deeper into the untamed wilderness.</Description>
      <Sector>Road</Sector>
      <Flags></Flags>
      <Exits>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>East</Direction>
          <Destination>50907</Destination>
          <Display>the door east</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>West</Direction>
          <Destination>50909</Destination>
          <Display>the door west</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
      </Exits>
      <ExtraDescriptions />
    </Room>
    <Room>
      <VNum>50909</VNum>
      <Name>The Forest Road</Name>
      <Description>The road stretches out before you, leading to the east towards civilization
and to the south further into the heart of the forest. The ground beneath
your feet is soft and springy, covered in a layer of fallen leaves and pine
needles. The air is cool and refreshing, carrying the scents of earth and
foliage. The forest around you is alive with activity, with the occasional
rustle of leaves and the distant call of a bird. The forest road itself is
well-worn, with deep ruts in the earth and occasional signs of travelers
passing through. Despite the feeling of isolation in the wilderness, there
is a sense of community and connection on the forest road. The road itself
is a symbol of the shared journey through the wild, with travelers from all
walks of life passing through. As you walk along the forest road, you feel
a sense of excitement and anticipation for the adventures that lie ahead.
To the east, the forest road leads towards civilization, with the promise
of safety and security. To the south, the forest road leads deeper into the
heart of the wilderness, offering the promise of further exploration and
discovery.</Description>
      <Sector>Road</Sector>
      <Flags></Flags>
      <Exits>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>East</Direction>
          <Destination>50908</Destination>
          <Display>the door east</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>South</Direction>
          <Destination>50910</Destination>
          <Display>the door south</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
      </Exits>
      <ExtraDescriptions />
    </Room>
    <Room>
      <VNum>50910</VNum>
      <Name>The Forest Road</Name>
      <Description>The path winds its way through a dense forest, with towering trees on
either side creating a natural archway overhead. The air is cool and fresh,
carrying the scents of pine and earth. Sunlight filters through the leaves,
casting dappled shadows on the path before you. Looking ahead, you can see
that the forest road continues to the north and south, leading deeper into
the heart of the wilderness. The path is well-maintained, with occasional
markers guiding the way. As you walk, you can hear the rustling of leaves
in the gentle breeze, along with the occasional bird call or rustling of
small animals in the underbrush. The forest around you is alive with
activity, with the occasional squirrel or rabbit darting across the path.</Description>
      <Sector>Road</Sector>
      <Flags></Flags>
      <Exits>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>North</Direction>
          <Destination>50909</Destination>
          <Display>the door north</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>South</Direction>
          <Destination>50911</Destination>
          <Display>the door south</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
      </Exits>
      <ExtraDescriptions />
    </Room>
    <Room>
      <VNum>50911</VNum>
      <Name>The Forest Road</Name>
      <Description>The path winds its way through a dense forest, with tall trees on either
side creating a natural canopy overhead. The air is cool and fresh,
carrying the scents of pine and earth. Sunlight filters through the leaves,
casting dappled shadows on the path before you. Looking ahead, you can see
that the forest road continues to the north and west, leading deeper into
the heart of the wilderness. The path is well-maintained, with occasional
markers guiding the way. As you walk, you can hear the rustling of leaves
in the gentle breeze, along with the occasional bird call or rustling of
small animals in the underbrush. The forest around you is alive with
activity, with the occasional squirrel or rabbit darting across the path.
Despite the feeling of solitude, there is a sense of safety and security on
the forest road, with the well-defined path providing a clear route through
the wilderness. The forest road invites you to explore further into the
natural world, offering a sense of adventure and possibility with each step
you take.</Description>
      <Sector>Road</Sector>
      <Flags></Flags>
      <Exits>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>North</Direction>
          <Destination>50910</Destination>
          <Display>the door north</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>West</Direction>
          <Destination>50912</Destination>
          <Display>the door west</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
      </Exits>
      <ExtraDescriptions />
    </Room>
    <Room>
      <VNum>50912</VNum>
      <Name>The Forest Road</Name>
      <Description>The road stretches out before you, leading to the east towards civilization
and to the south further into the heart of the forest. The ground beneath
your feet is soft and springy, covered in a layer of fallen leaves and pine
needles. The air is cool and refreshing, carrying the scents of earth and
foliage. The forest around you is alive with activity, with the occasional
rustle of leaves and the distant call of a bird. The forest road itself is
well-worn, with deep ruts in the earth and occasional signs of travelers
passing through. Despite the feeling of isolation in the wilderness, there
is a sense of community and connection on the forest road. The road itself
is a symbol of the shared journey through the wild, with travelers from all
walks of life passing through. As you walk along the forest road, you feel
a sense of excitement and anticipation for the adventures that lie ahead.
To the east, the forest road leads towards civilization, with the promise
of safety and security. To the south, the forest road leads deeper into the
heart of the wilderness, offering the promise of further exploration and
discovery.</Description>
      <Sector>Road</Sector>
      <Flags></Flags>
      <Exits>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>East</Direction>
          <Destination>50911</Destination>
          <Display>the door east</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>South</Direction>
          <Destination>50913</Destination>
          <Display>the door south</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
      </Exits>
      <ExtraDescriptions />
    </Room>
    <Room>
      <VNum>50913</VNum>
      <Name>The Forest Road</Name>
      <Description>The road stretches out before you, leading to the north towards
civilization and to the west deeper into the heart of the forest. The
ground beneath your feet is soft and springy, covered in a layer of fallen
leaves and pine needles. The air is cool and refreshing, carrying the
scents of earth and foliage. The forest around you is alive with activity,
with the occasional rustle of leaves and the distant call of a bird. The
forest road itself is well-worn, with deep ruts in the earth and occasional
signs of travelers passing through. Despite the feeling of isolation in the
wilderness, there is a sense of community and connection on the forest
road. The road itself is a symbol of the shared journey through the wild,
with travelers from all walks of life passing through. As you walk along
the forest road, you feel a sense of excitement and anticipation for the
adventures that lie ahead. To the north, the forest road leads towards
civilization, offering the promise of safety and comfort. To the west, the
forest road leads deeper into the heart of the wilderness, offering the
promise of further exploration and discovery.</Description>
      <Sector>Road</Sector>
      <Flags></Flags>
      <Exits>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>North</Direction>
          <Destination>50912</Destination>
          <Display>the door north</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>West</Direction>
          <Destination>50914</Destination>
          <Display>the door west</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
      </Exits>
      <ExtraDescriptions />
    </Room>
    <Room>
      <VNum>50914</VNum>
      <Name>The Forest Road</Name>
      <Description>The road stretches out before you, leading to the east towards civilization
and to the south further into the heart of the forest. The ground beneath
your feet is soft and springy, covered in a layer of fallen leaves and pine
needles. The air is cool and refreshing, carrying the scents of earth and
foliage. The forest around you is alive with activity, with the occasional
rustle of leaves and the distant call of a bird. The forest road itself is
well-worn, with deep ruts in the earth and occasional signs of travelers
passing through. Despite the feeling of isolation in the wilderness, there
is a sense of community and connection on the forest road. The road itself
is a symbol of the shared journey through the wild, with travelers from all
walks of life passing through. As you walk along the forest road, you feel
a sense of excitement and anticipation for the adventures that lie ahead.
To the east, the forest road leads towards civilization, with the promise
of safety and security. To the south, the forest road leads deeper into the
heart of the wilderness, offering the promise of further exploration and
discovery.</Description>
      <Sector>Road</Sector>
      <Flags></Flags>
      <Exits>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>East</Direction>
          <Destination>50913</Destination>
          <Display>the door east</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>South</Direction>
          <Destination>50915</Destination>
          <Display>the door south</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
      </Exits>
      <ExtraDescriptions />
    </Room>
    <Room>
      <VNum>50915</VNum>
      <Name>The Forest Road</Name>
      <Description>The road stretches out before you, leading to the east and west deeper into
the forest. To the north, you can see the signs of civilization, offering
the promise of safety and comfort. The ground beneath your feet is soft and
springy, covered in a layer of fallen leaves and pine needles. The air is
cool and refreshing, carrying the scents of earth and foliage. The forest
around you is alive with activity, with the occasional rustle of leaves and
the distant call of a bird. The forest road itself is well-worn, with deep
ruts in the earth and occasional signs of travelers passing through.
Despite the feeling of isolation in the wilderness, there is a sense of
community and connection on the forest road. The road itself is a symbol of
the shared journey through the wild, with travelers from all walks of life
passing through. As you walk along the forest road, you feel a sense of
excitement and anticipation for the adventures that lie ahead. To the east
and west, the forest road leads deeper into the heart of the wilderness,
offering the promise of further exploration and discovery. To the north,
civilization awaits, with the promise of safety and security.</Description>
      <Sector>Road</Sector>
      <Flags></Flags>
      <Exits>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>North</Direction>
          <Destination>50914</Destination>
          <Display>the door north</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>East</Direction>
          <Destination>50916</Destination>
          <Display>the door east</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>West</Direction>
          <Destination>50923</Destination>
          <Display>the door west</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
      </Exits>
      <ExtraDescriptions />
    </Room>
    <Room>
      <VNum>50916</VNum>
      <Name>The Forest Road</Name>
      <Description>The road stretches out before you, leading to the west towards civilization
and to the south deeper into the heart of the forest. The ground beneath
your feet is soft and springy, covered in a layer of fallen leaves and pine
needles. The air is cool and refreshing, carrying the scents of earth and
foliage. The forest around you is alive with activity, with the occasional
rustle of leaves and the distant call of a bird. The forest road itself is
well-worn, with deep ruts in the earth and occasional signs of travelers
passing through. Despite the feeling of isolation in the wilderness, there
is a sense of community and connection on the forest road. The road itself
is a symbol of the shared journey through the wild, with travelers from all
walks of life passing through. As you walk along the forest road, you feel
a sense of excitement and anticipation for the adventures that lie ahead.
To the west, the forest road leads towards civilization, offering the
promise of safety and comfort. To the south, the forest road leads deeper
into the heart of the wilderness, offering the promise of further
exploration and discovery.</Description>
      <Sector>Road</Sector>
      <Flags></Flags>
      <Exits>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>South</Direction>
          <Destination>50917</Destination>
          <Display>the door south</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>West</Direction>
          <Destination>50915</Destination>
          <Display>the door west</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
      </Exits>
      <ExtraDescriptions />
    </Room>
    <Room>
      <VNum>50917</VNum>
      <Name>The Forest Road</Name>
      <Description>The path winds its way through a dense forest, with towering trees on
either side creating a natural archway overhead. The air is cool and fresh,
carrying the scents of pine and earth. Sunlight filters through the leaves,
casting dappled shadows on the path before you. Looking ahead, you can see
that the forest road continues to the north and south, leading deeper into
the heart of the wilderness. The path is well-maintained, with occasional
markers guiding the way. As you walk, you can hear the rustling of leaves
in the gentle breeze, along with the occasional bird call or rustling of
small animals in the underbrush. The forest around you is alive with
activity, with the occasional squirrel or rabbit darting across the path.</Description>
      <Sector>Road</Sector>
      <Flags></Flags>
      <Exits>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>North</Direction>
          <Destination>50916</Destination>
          <Display>the door north</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>South</Direction>
          <Destination>50918</Destination>
          <Display>the door south</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
      </Exits>
      <ExtraDescriptions />
    </Room>
    <Room>
      <VNum>50918</VNum>
      <Name>The Forest Road</Name>
      <Description>The path winds its way through a dense forest, with towering trees on
either side forming a natural canopy overhead. The air is cool and crisp,
carrying the scents of pine and earth. Sunlight filters down through the
leaves, casting dappled shadows on the path before you. Looking ahead, you
can see that the forest road continues to the north and west, beckoning you
deeper into the heart of the wilderness. The path is well-maintained, with
occasional markers guiding the way. As you walk, you can hear the rustling
of leaves in the gentle breeze, along with the occasional bird call or
rustling of small animals in the underbrush. The forest around you is alive
with activity, with the occasional squirrel or rabbit darting across the
path. Despite the feeling of solitude, there is a sense of safety and
security on the forest road, with the well-defined path providing a clear
route through the wilderness. The forest road invites you to explore
further into the natural world, offering a sense of adventure and
possibility with each step you take. The north and westward direction of
the path gives a sense of exploration and discovery, as you journey deeper
into the unknown depths of the forest.</Description>
      <Sector>Road</Sector>
      <Flags></Flags>
      <Exits>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>North</Direction>
          <Destination>50917</Destination>
          <Display>the door north</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>West</Direction>
          <Destination>50919</Destination>
          <Display>the door west</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
      </Exits>
      <ExtraDescriptions />
    </Room>
    <Room>
      <VNum>50919</VNum>
      <Name>The Forest Road</Name>
      <Description>The path winds its way through a dense forest, with tall trees on either
side forming a natural canopy overhead. The air is cool and refreshing,
carrying the scents of pine and earth. Sunlight filters through the leaves,
casting dappled shadows on the path before you. Looking ahead, you can see
that the forest road continues to the east and west, offering two distinct
paths through the wilderness. The path is well-maintained, with occasional
markers guiding the way. As you walk, you can hear the rustling of leaves
in the gentle breeze, along with the occasional bird call or rustling of
small animals in the underbrush. The forest around you is alive with
activity, with the occasional squirrel or rabbit darting across the path.
Despite the feeling of solitude, there is a sense of safety and security on
the forest road, with the well-defined path providing a clear route through
the wilderness.</Description>
      <Sector>Road</Sector>
      <Flags></Flags>
      <Exits>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>East</Direction>
          <Destination>50918</Destination>
          <Display>the door east</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>West</Direction>
          <Destination>50920</Destination>
          <Display>the door west</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
      </Exits>
      <ExtraDescriptions />
    </Room>
    <Room>
      <VNum>50920</VNum>
      <Name>The Forest Road</Name>
      <Description>The path winds its way through a dense forest, with tall trees on either
side forming a natural canopy overhead. The air is cool and fresh, carrying
the scents of pine and earth. Sunlight filters through the leaves, casting
dappled shadows on the path before you. Looking ahead, you can see that the
forest road continues to the east and south, leading deeper into the heart
of the wilderness. The path is well-maintained, with occasional markers
guiding the way. As you walk, you can hear the rustling of leaves in the
gentle breeze, along with the occasional bird call or rustling of small
animals in the underbrush. The forest around you is alive with activity,
with the occasional squirrel or rabbit darting across the path. Despite the
feeling of solitude, there is a sense of safety and security on the forest
road, with the well-defined path providing a clear route through the
wilderness. The forest road invites you to explore further into the natural
world, with the east and southward directions offering the promise of new
adventures and discoveries.</Description>
      <Sector>Road</Sector>
      <Flags></Flags>
      <Exits>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>East</Direction>
          <Destination>50919</Destination>
          <Display>the door east</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>South</Direction>
          <Destination>50921</Destination>
          <Display>the door south</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
      </Exits>
      <ExtraDescriptions />
    </Room>
    <Room>
      <VNum>50921</VNum>
      <Name>The Forest Road</Name>
      <Description>The path winds its way through a dense forest, with towering trees on
either side creating a natural archway overhead. The air is cool and fresh,
carrying the scents of pine and earth. Sunlight filters through the leaves,
casting dappled shadows on the path before you. Looking ahead, you can see
that the forest road continues to the north and south, leading deeper into
the heart of the wilderness. The path is well-maintained, with occasional
markers guiding the way. As you walk, you can hear the rustling of leaves
in the gentle breeze, along with the occasional bird call or rustling of
small animals in the underbrush. The forest around you is alive with
activity, with the occasional squirrel or rabbit darting across the path.</Description>
      <Sector>Road</Sector>
      <Flags></Flags>
      <Exits>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>North</Direction>
          <Destination>50920</Destination>
          <Display>the door north</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>South</Direction>
          <Destination>50922</Destination>
          <Display>the door south</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
      </Exits>
      <ExtraDescriptions />
    </Room>
    <Room>
      <VNum>50922</VNum>
      <Name>The Forest Road</Name>
      <Description>The path winds its way through a dense forest, with towering trees on
either side creating a natural archway overhead. The air is cool and fresh,
carrying the scents of pine and earth. Sunlight filters through the leaves,
casting dappled shadows on the path before you. Looking ahead, you can see
that the forest road continues to the north and south, leading deeper into
the heart of the wilderness. The path is well-maintained, with occasional
markers guiding the way. As you walk, you can hear the rustling of leaves
in the gentle breeze, along with the occasional bird call or rustling of
small animals in the underbrush. The forest around you is alive with
activity, with the occasional squirrel or rabbit darting across the path.</Description>
      <Sector>Road</Sector>
      <Flags></Flags>
      <Exits>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>North</Direction>
          <Destination>50921</Destination>
          <Display>the door north</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>South</Direction>
          <Destination>51000</Destination>
          <Display>the door south</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
      </Exits>
      <ExtraDescriptions />
    </Room>
    <Room>
      <VNum>50923</VNum>
      <Name>The Forest Road</Name>
      <Description></Description>
      <Sector>Road</Sector>
      <Flags></Flags>
      <Exits>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>East</Direction>
          <Destination>50915</Destination>
          <Display>the door east</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>South</Direction>
          <Destination>50924</Destination>
          <Display>the door south</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
      </Exits>
      <ExtraDescriptions />
    </Room>
    <Room>
      <VNum>50924</VNum>
      <Name>The Forest Road</Name>
      <Description></Description>
      <Sector>Road</Sector>
      <Flags></Flags>
      <Exits>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>North</Direction>
          <Destination>50923</Destination>
          <Display>the door north</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>South</Direction>
          <Destination>50925</Destination>
          <Display>the door south</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
      </Exits>
      <ExtraDescriptions />
    </Room>
    <Room>
      <VNum>50925</VNum>
      <Name>The Forest Road</Name>
      <Description></Description>
      <Sector>Road</Sector>
      <Flags></Flags>
      <Exits>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>North</Direction>
          <Destination>50924</Destination>
          <Display>the door north</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>West</Direction>
          <Destination>50926</Destination>
          <Display>the door west</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
      </Exits>
      <ExtraDescriptions />
    </Room>
    <Room>
      <VNum>50926</VNum>
      <Name>The Forest Road</Name>
      <Description></Description>
      <Sector>Road</Sector>
      <Flags></Flags>
      <Exits>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>East</Direction>
          <Destination>50925</Destination>
          <Display>the door east</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>West</Direction>
          <Destination>50927</Destination>
          <Display>the door west</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
      </Exits>
      <ExtraDescriptions />
    </Room>
    <Room>
      <VNum>50927</VNum>
      <Name>The Forest Road</Name>
      <Description></Description>
      <Sector>Road</Sector>
      <Flags></Flags>
      <Exits>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>East</Direction>
          <Destination>50926</Destination>
          <Display>the door east</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
        <Exit>
          <Direction>South</Direction>
          <Destination>17899</Destination>
          <Display>the door south</Display>
          <Keywords></Keywords>
          <Description></Description>
          <Flags></Flags>
          <Keys></Keys>
          <ExitSize>Giant</ExitSize>
        </Exit>
      </Exits>
      <ExtraDescriptions />
    </Room>
  </Rooms>
  <NPCs />
  <Items />
  <Resets />
</Area>