<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Area>
  <AreaData>
    <Name>Help</Name>
    <Info></Info>
    <VnumStart>1100000</VnumStart>
    <VnumEnd>1100099</VnumEnd>
    <Builders></Builders>
    <Security>0</Security>
    <Credits></Credits>
    <OverRoomVnum>0</OverRoomVnum>
  </AreaData>
  <Rooms />
  <NPCs />
  <Items />
  <Resets />
  <Helps>
    <Help VNum="1100000" Level="1" Keyword="peek" LastEditedBy="" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:19:44">When looking at someone, a thief attempts to peek at their inventory.</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100005" Level="1" Keyword="'enhanced damage'" LastEditedBy="" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:19:44">Chance per hit to increase damage.</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100010" Level="1" Keyword="'enhanced damage ii'" LastEditedBy="" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:19:44">When enhanced damage chance succeeds, gain another chance per hit to increase damage further.</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100015" Level="1" Keyword="spellcraft" LastEditedBy="" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:19:44">Chance per spell cast to increase damage.</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100020" Level="1" Keyword="'spellcraft ii'" LastEditedBy="" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:19:44">Increases spellcrafts chance to be successful.</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100025" Level="1" Keyword="'fast healing'" LastEditedBy="" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:19:44">Chance to increase rate of healing in all positions.</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100030" Level="1" Keyword="meditation" LastEditedBy="" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:19:44">Chance to increase rate of mana gained in all positions.</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100035" Level="1" Keyword="trance" LastEditedBy="" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:19:44">Chance to increase rate of mana gained in all positions.</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100040" Level="1" Keyword="'rogues awareness'" LastEditedBy="" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:19:44">Chance to know which direction you flee in.</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100045" Level="1" Keyword="'gentle walk'" LastEditedBy="" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:19:44">Chance that an aggressive npc will ignore your entrance.</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100050" Level="1" Keyword="flourintine" LastEditedBy="" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:19:44">Increases chance to parry while dual wielding swords.</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100055" Level="1" Keyword="distance" LastEditedBy="" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:19:44">Chance to keep your enemy from hitting you while using a polearm.</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100060" Level="1" Keyword="'defensive spin'" LastEditedBy="" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:19:44">Increases chance to avoid damage while wielding a staff or spear.</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100065" Level="1" Keyword="riposte" LastEditedBy="" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:19:44">You gain a chance to return some damage for eacy parry while wielding a sword.</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100070" Level="1" Keyword="survivalist" LastEditedBy="" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:19:44">Reduces the need for food and water.</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100075" Level="1" Keyword="'quiet movement'" LastEditedBy="" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:19:44">Prevents others from seeing which direction you left in or came from.</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100080" Level="1" Keyword="'path finding'" LastEditedBy="" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:19:44">Chance to reduce movement points spent while moving within wilderness,
this effect is spread to the entire party when leader has this skill.</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100085" Level="1" Keyword="'minor regeneration'" LastEditedBy="" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:19:44">Chance to heal a small amount between each pulse (250ms).</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100090" Level="1" Keyword="'major regeration'" LastEditedBy="" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:19:44">Chance to heal a medium amount between each pulse (250ms).</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100095" Level="1" Keyword="'greater regeration'" LastEditedBy="" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:19:44">Chance to heal a moderate amount between each pulse (250ms).</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100100" Level="1" Keyword="'super regeration'" LastEditedBy="" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:19:44">Chance to heal a generous amount between each pulse (250ms).</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100105" Level="1" Keyword="'combat steal'" LastEditedBy="" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:19:44">Stealing can now be successful while in combat with the victim.</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100110" Level="1" Keyword="'prey on the weak'" LastEditedBy="" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:19:44">Thieves have learned to take advantage of weak opponents.  As their victim gets 
closer to death, they push their advantage striking harder blows.</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100115" Level="1" Keyword="'acrobatics'" LastEditedBy="" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:19:44">Thieves that have become agile and fast because of their pickpocket habits 
learn to avoid certain blows from other, more warrior-like opponents.  Thieves 
with this skill have been known to avoid bashes, trips, throws, and 
surprising attacks such as ambush, charge, etc.</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100120" Level="1" Keyword="'enliven'" LastEditedBy="" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:19:44">Shapeshifters can enliven certain spells while in form without costing mana. For example,
if the spell "fly" expires while in form, when out of combat a shapeshifter can
"enliven fly" to "recast" the spell while in form.</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100125" Level="1" Keyword="'recover of the snake'" LastEditedBy="" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:19:44">A greater enliven for focus major utility, increases health regeneration while
in form, equivalent major regeneration.</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100130" Level="1" Keyword="'tiger frenzy'" LastEditedBy="" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:19:44">A greater enliven for focus major offensive, increases strength and dexterity
while in form.</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100135" Level="1" Keyword="'bestial fury'" LastEditedBy="" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:19:44">A greater enliven for focus major offensive, increases all damage while in form
by 25%.</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100140" Level="1" Keyword="'primal tenacity'" LastEditedBy="" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:19:44">A greater enliven for focus major defensive, increases SavingBreath,
SavingPetrification, SavingRod, and SavingSpells. Additional resistance
to mental and negative attacks.</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100145" Level="1" Keyword="'skin of the displacer'" LastEditedBy="" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:19:44">A greater enliven for focus major defensive, which gives a small chance to
evade any type of damage, magical or physical.</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100155" Level="0" Keyword="help" LastEditedBy="Giaken" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:30:40.4362348-05:00">Type 'help [keyword]' to get help on a specific keyword.
Type `help list` to get a list of all the help entries.
Some topics you could get help on is communication, combat, skills, and
training.</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100165" Level="0" Keyword="communication" LastEditedBy="Giaken" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:31:10.5775226-05:00">Type 'newbie [text]' to ask or answer questions on the newbie channel.
Type 'say [text]' to speak to the current room.
Type 'whisper [text]' to speak to the current room without unhiding.
Type 'tell [playername] [text]' to talk to an individual player.
Type 'yell [text]' to yell a message to the current area.
Type 'pray [text]' to send a message to the gods.</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100175" Level="0" Keyword="combat" LastEditedBy="Giaken" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:33:08.3737458-05:00">Type 'consider [name]' to see how an NPC's level compares to your own.
Type 'kill [name]' to initiate combat with a creature.
Some NPCs are aggressive and will attack you when you walk in.
Type the name of a skill to perform it in combat if applicable, for example
'kick' while already fighting to perform your kick move.
Mages can 'cast [spellname] [target]' to use their spells.
Bards can 'sing [song name]' to sing their songs during combat.</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100185" Level="0" Keyword="MOTD" LastEditedBy="Giaken" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:36:11.314389-05:00">New 'bug' command to report bugs to the gods.
New 'map' command to draw an ascii map of the surrounding area.
Typing 'help' now has a default help entry.
'Toggle' command to change flags such as Auto Loot, or Color
Check out the website https://kbs-cloud.com for a map and more
duelchallenge - Issue a duel challenge to another player.
duelaccept - Accept a duel challenge from another player.
duelcancel - Decline a duel challenge from another player.
AFK flag added. No longer get hungry or thirsty
after being inactive for five minutes.
Typing `help list` will list all help entries
Map now displays trainers, shops and healers.
New replay command to replay the last 20 communications
</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100195" Level="0" Keyword="skills spells songs supplications" LastEditedBy="Giaken" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:44:03.1718596-05:00">You can type 'practice' to see a list of all skills, spells and songs you
can currently use. Type 'practice [skill/spell/song]' at a guildmaster to
learn an ability better.
You can type 'skills', 'spells', 'songs' or 'supplications' to see a list
of all the abilities you will ever learn.
Mages use 'cast [ability]' to cast spells. Priestly guilds
use 'commune [ability]' to use their prayers. Bards use 'sing [ability]' to
sing their repertoire of songs.</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100205" Level="0" Keyword="train gain training stats" LastEditedBy="Giaken" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:47:53.3265624-05:00">You can train at a trainer or in some cases, at your guildmaster.
You start with base stats for your race. These are strength,
intelligence, wisdom, dexterity, constitution and charisma.
These stats affect multiple aspects such as how much(weight/count) you
can carry, how much you learn when practicing and how many hitpoints
you will gain when you level.
Type 'train' at a trainer to get a list of what is available to you to train.
Each race has maximum values a stat can be raised to.
You can type 'gain convert' to convert 10 practices into a train.
You can type 'gain revert' to revert a train into 10 practices.
You start with 3 trains and gain 1 train every 5 levels.</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100215" Level="0" Keyword="races human elf dwarf orc minotaur" LastEditedBy="Giaken" LastEditedOn="2023-08-19T19:22:39.3798516-05:00">Elf      - starting stats  - 16 str 19 wis 23 int 19 dex 16 con 18 chr
         - max stats       - 17 str 20 wis 25 int 22 dex 16 con 18 chr
          (classes) warrior, paladin, healer, mage, shapeshifter, 
           thief, bard, ranger, assassin)

human    - starting stats  - 18 str 18 wis 18 int 18 dex 18 con 18 chr
         - max stats       - 20 str 20 wis 20 int 20 dex 20 con 20 chr
          (classes) warrior, paladin, healer, mage, shapeshifter, 
           thief, bard, ranger, assassin)

dwarf    - starting stats  - 20 str 18 wis 18 int 16 dex 24 con 15 chr
         - max stats       - 22 str 18 wis 18 int 17 dex 25 con 16 chr
          (classes) warrior, paladin, healer, bard, ranger, assassin)

orc      - starting stats  -  21 str 15 wis 16 int 19 dex 21 con  8 chr
         - max stats       - 23 str 17 wis 17 int 20 dex 23 con 12 chr
          (classes) warrior, healer, thief, bard, ranger, assassin)

minotaur - starting stats  - 21 str 16 wis 17 int 16 dex 20 con 12 chr
         - max stats       - 23 str 18 wis 18 int 18 dex 22 con 12 chr
          (classes) none</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100225" Level="0" Keyword="classes guilds warrior paladin thief bard mage shapeshifter ranger healer assassin" LastEditedBy="Giaken" LastEditedOn="2023-08-19T19:42:36.0396669-05:00">warrior - focus on weapon specialization, decent at taking and 
dealing damage. Gets a weapon specialization at level 20 and 40.
Must be proficient in use of a weapon to specialize in it.
Can shield block, dodge, parry and feint blows.

assassin - focus on martial arts, gets improved kicks upon mastering
earlier ones. Can dodge and parry. Can bind wounds when injured.

mage - focus on perfecting elements. Unlock new elemental spells as
you master earlier spells.

shapeshifter - focus on changing into the forms of animals. First
form at level 5 - 8, must have a shapefocus major chosen.

thief - great at subterfuge, does better as a sidekick someone else
standing in the fore. Can knock enemies out and bind their hands and
legs. Can hide and sneak past some enemies and pick locks to open doors
and containers.

healer - great at cleansing maladies and restoring the health of their
friends. Can grant flight, sanctuary, blessings and a battle frenzy.

paladin - known for taking lead and standing in the fore of combat. They
can grant themselves sanctuary. Choose whether to do more damage using
a two handed weapon or block damage with a one handed weapon and a shield.

bard - boost the morale and health of your party, dash the spirits of your
foes and cause them harm with offensive lyrics.

ranger - excel in the forests, caves, mountains and deserts of the world.
Find and gather herbs for yourself or your party members to heal wounds.
Take cover hiding yourself and ambush your prey in the wild. Explore the
wilds, getting less tired as you move through them. Can fashion their own
weapons in the wild and eventually be able to imbue them, causing them to
heal during combat.</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100235" Level="0" Keyword="alignment good neutral evil" LastEditedBy="Giaken" LastEditedOn="2023-08-19T20:02:51.1818461-05:00">Good: Characters who are aligned with "good" believe in altruism, respect
for life, and a desire to help others. They tend to make choices that
benefit not just themselves but also those around them, often at their own
expense. Good characters are compassionate and will often go out of their
way to prevent harm to innocents. They uphold values of kindness, charity,
and self-sacrifice. 

Neutral: Neutral characters tend to be more pragmatic
and do not feel a strong pull towards either extreme of good or evil. Their
actions may be driven by personal gain, a sense of balance, or the specific
situation at hand rather than an inherent moral code. Neutral characters
might believe in a natural balance and might act to restore that balance if
they feel it's been disrupted. They may also prioritize their own
well-being or the well-being of their close companions over broader ethical
or moral considerations. 

Evil: Characters who are "evil" prioritize their
own needs and desires over those of others and may be willing to harm or
manipulate others to achieve their goals. They might be driven by greed,
power, anger, hatred, or a desire for revenge. Evil characters might not
necessarily be cruel or violent, but they tend to lack empathy for others,
especially if there's a conflict between their interests and the well-being
of others. It's worth noting that these alignments serve as broad
categories, and within them, there can be a lot of variation. For example,
one "good" character might be driven by a strong sense of justice, while
another might prioritize mercy. Similarly, an "evil" character could be a
ruthless tyrant or a cunning manipulator. The alignment system helps
players think about their characters' motivations and can guide
decision-making within the game, but it's always up to individual
interpretation.

Good and evil characters receive bonus experience for
slaying a character of the opposite alignment.</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100245" Level="0" Keyword="ethos orderly neutral chaotic" LastEditedBy="Giaken" LastEditedOn="2023-08-19T20:09:18.9752668-05:00">Lawful (often referred to as Orderly): Characters with a lawful alignment
believe in a structured society, rules, order, and tradition. They value
discipline, responsibility, and adherence to a set code of behavior,
whether personal or dictated by a governing body. Lawful characters might
respect authority, keep their promises, and try to always act within the
confines of the law. Their predictability is both a strength and a
weakness. It's important to note that "lawful" doesn't necessarily mean
"good"; a character can be lawful and evil, adhering strictly to a code or
set of laws that are oppressive or harmful. 

Neutral (with respect to ethos): Neutral characters, in terms of ethos, fall 
between the extremes of lawfulness and chaos. They might respect order and 
authority when it suits them or their goals but don't inherently adhere to 
them. Similarly, they don't actively seek to disrupt order or sow chaos. 
Their actions are often driven by what seems appropriate at the moment, 
making them flexible and pragmatic. They tend to prioritize personal 
freedom and will generally go with whatever system or approach offers 
them the best balance of security and freedom. 

Chaotic: Chaotic characters value individual freedom over
structure and order. They are skeptical of authority and often resist
rules, regulations, and traditions, seeing them as constraints. They
prioritize personal freedom and often act based on their whims or personal
desires rather than any external code of behavior. Like with the lawful
alignment, "chaotic" does not inherently mean "evil"; a chaotic good
character, for example, might defy oppressive laws to do what they believe
is right.</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100250" Level="52" Keyword="OLC create edit dig saveworld worldsave" LastEditedBy="" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:19:44">Commands are:
Create
create area [name] [vnumstart] [vnumend]
		create room [vnum]
		create npc [vnum]
		create item [vnum]
			Or: create reset [vnum] [desintation] [count] [maxcount]

Edit
edit area [name]

edit room [vnum]
edit room [name|description|sector|exits] {{value}

sectors are inside, city, forest, field, hills, mountain, swamp, 
desert, cave, underground, waterswim, waternoswim, river, ocean, air, road, underwater

Edit room exits {{direction} [keywords, description, destination, flags, size, keys, delete] {{arguments}

edit npc [vnum]
edit npc [name|description|level|gold|longdescription|shortdescription|flags|
damagedice|guild|protects|hitpointdice|manapointdice|affectedby] {{value}

flags are Practice NoAlign ColorOn SkipAutoDeletePrompt AutoAssist AutoExit AutoLoot AutoSac 
	AutoGold AutoSplit Evaluation Betrayer HeroImm HolyLight CanLoot NoSummon NoFollow NoTransfer 
	PlayerDenied Frozen AssistPlayer AssistAll AssistVnum AssistAlign AssistRace Sentinel Scavenger 
	CabalMob Aggressive Stay_Area Stay_Area Wimpy Pet Trainer Trainer Trainer NoTrack Undead 
	Cleric Mage Thief Warrior NoPurge Outdoors Indoors IsHealer Banker Brief NPC Changer Healer 
	Shopkeeper Area_Attack

affectflags are Blind, Invisible, DetectEvil, DetectEvil, DetectInvis, DetectInvis, DetectMagic, 
DetectMagic, Detect_Hidden, Detect_Hidden, Detect_Good, Detect_Good, DetectIllusion, DetectIllusion, 
Sanctuary, Faerie_Fire, Infrared, Curse, Poison, Protect_Evil, ProtectionGood, Sneak, Hide, Sleep, 
Charm, Flying, PassDoor, Haste, Calm, Plague, Weaken, DarkVision, Berserk, Swim, Regeneration, Slow, 
Camouflage

edit item [vnum]
Edit Item [vnum] [name|description|level|extraflags|wearflags|itemtypes|value|
nutrition|maxcharges|liquid|material|affects] {{value}

extra flags are Glow Hum Dark Lock Locked Evil Invisibility Invisibility Magic NoDrop 
Bless AntiGood AntiNeutral AntiEvil NoRemove NoPurge RotDeath VisDeath Fixed NoDisarm 
NoLocate MeltDrop Closable Closeable PickProof Closed WeaponFlaming Poison Heart 
PouchNourishment EverfullSkin BurnProof Flaming Frost Vorpal Shocking Unholy Sharp 
TwoHands NoUncurse SellExtract PutIn PutOn PutAt StandAt StandOn SitAt SitIn SitOn 
RestIn RestOn RestAt SleepAt SleepOn SleepIn Inventory Outfit

wear flags are Take Finger About Neck Head Legs Feet Hands Wield Hold WearFloat WearFloat 
Tattoo Body Waist Wrist Arms Shield NoSac
*** Take is required to pick up an item

itemtypes are Silver Gold Light Scroll Wand Staff Weapon Treasure Armor Potion Clothing 
Furniture Trash Container DrinkContainer Key Food Money Boat NPCCorpse Corpse 
Fountain Pill Map Portal RoomKey Gem Jewelry Cabal Instrument Skeleton

Dig
dig [direction] [vnum] {{flags}
flags are: door closed locked window pickproof nopass nobash hidden

NextVnum
displays the next vnum to use for rooms, npcs or items in an area

Worldsave or Saveworld will save modified areas</Help>
    <Help VNum="1100255" Level="1" Keyword="prompt" LastEditedBy="" LastEditedOn="2023-08-07T14:19:44">Syntax: prompt
Syntax: prompt default
Syntax: prompt all
	same as `prompt default`
Syntax: prompt &lt;%*&gt;
 
PROMPT with out an argument will turn your prompt on or off.
 
PROMPT ALL will give you the standard "&lt;hits mana moves&gt;" prompt.
 
PROMPT &lt;%*&gt; where the %* are the various variables you may set yourself.
        %1 :  Display % of hitpoints
        %2 :  Display % of mana
        %3 :  Display % of movement
        %h :  Display your current hits
        %H :  Display your maximum hits
        %m :  Display your current mana
        %M :  Display your maximum mana
        %v :  Display your current moves
        %V :  Display your maximum moves
        %x :  Display your current experience
        %X :  Display experience to level
        %g :  Display your gold held
        %s :  Display silver carried
        %a :  Display your alignment
        %r :  Display the room name you are in
        %e :  Display the exits from the room in NESWDU style
        %c :  Display a carriage return (useful for multi-line prompts)
        %R :  Display the vnum you are in (IMMORTAL ONLY)
        %z :  Display the area name you are in (IMMORTAL ONLY)
 
Example: PROMPT &lt;%hhp %mm %vmv&gt;
Will set your prompt to "&lt;10hp 100m 100mv&gt;"</Help>
  </Helps>
</Area>